jamonkey.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy - JaMonkey - Atlanta Mom Blogger | Parenting & Lifestyle

### Privacy Policy

We value and respect our visitors privacy. That is the reason why we included this privacy policy to make sure that your privacy is not being violated. If you have any questions concerning our Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to ask!

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
This site gives users the option to remove their information from our mailing list database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive my service. Instructions on how to do this are sent within every email communication from JaMonkey.

**Google and the**[ **DoubleClick DART cookie**](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx)

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Advertising Networks  
**We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

**Contacting Me  
**If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this blog, fill out my [contact form.](http://jamonkey.com/contact-me/ "Contact Me")

Please keep in mind we abide by all FTC and Google guidelines in order to stay compliant.
